Guide to the Duke Gardens Foundation records, 1912-2002 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
- Architectural Records, 1912-1982 and undated (Box 119)
  - Sill & Roof Plans, Greenhouse Sections, #2. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1971 May 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6a, Box 119)
  - Elevations and Sections, #3. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1971 May 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6a, Box 119)
  - Persian Garden F.S. Side Details, #4. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1971 Apr 30. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6a, Box 119)
  - Persian Garden Ridge & Roof Det.s, #5. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1971 May 6. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6a, Box 119)
  - F.S. Side Details, Re-Skin Exist Struct, #6. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1971 May 11. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6a, Box 119)
  - Ridge & Room Details to Apply New Alum. Skin on Existing Structure, #7. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1971 May 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6a, Box 119)
  - Gable & Corner Details, #8. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1971 May 18. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6a, Box 119)
  - Valley Connection Details, #9. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1971 May 20. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6a, Box 119)
  - Greenhouse Roof & Gable Ends Between Two Curved Eave Greenhouses, Dr'g 1. Lord & Burnham/ L.I.D. 1961 Jan 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6a, Box 119)
  - [Gutter & Rafter Details], Dr'g 2. Lord & Burnham/ L.I.D. 1961 Jan 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6a, Box 119)
  - [Ridge & Roof Details], Dr'g 3. Lord & Burnham/ L.I.D. 1961 Jan 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6a, Box 119)
  - [Gutters, Rafters & Ridges], Dr'g 4. Lord & Burnham/ L.I.D. 1961 Jan 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6a, Box 119)
  - [Gutter & Rafter Details], Dr'g 5. Lord & Burnham/ L.I.D. 1961 Jan 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6b, Box 119)
  - [Gutters, Rafters, Gablebars, Purlins], Dr'g 6. Lord & Burnham/ L.I.D. 1961 Jan 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6b, Box 119)
  - Plan at Gable Door Jamb, Dr'g 7. Lord & Burnham/ L.I.D. 1961 Jan 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6b, Box 119)
  - Gutter Outlet & Downspout Details, Dr'g 8. Lord & Burnham/ L.I.D. 1961 Jan 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6b, Box 119)
  - Detail of Hanger at Gable Ridge Vents For Rigid Frame Construction #5146. HB. 1965 Dec 18. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6b, Box 119)
  - Nice Bearing Hanger for Rigid Frame - Mark II. Lord & Burnham/B. 1960 Mar 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6b, Box 119)
  - Installation Details - Powervent Type L-363-VR Arm & Rod. Lord & Burnham. 1957 Nov 18. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6b, Box 119)
  - Mark II-R Powervent Type L-588-V-R-P. Lord & Burnham/B. 1960 Jun 21; 1960 Aug 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6b, Box 119)
  - Proposed 11 Ft. Gro-Mor-"A". Lord & Burnham/PLC. 1960 Jan 26. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6b, Box 119)
  - Proposed Plastic Gromore. Lord & Burnham/John Hecho. 1961 Nov 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F6b, Box 119)
  - Valley Connection Details 18'-G'Hse, Dwg. 10. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1971 May 21. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Italian Garden Restoration, Greenhouse #24, Greenhouse Sill Plan, Dwg. #A1. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1972 Nov 29. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Greenhouse Roof Plan, Italian Garden, Ghse #24, Dwg. A2. Lord & Burnham. 1972 Dec 14. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Greenhouse Elevations, Italian Garden, G'h'se. #24, Dwg. A3. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1972 Dec 27. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Greenhouse Section/Italian Garden, Section, Dwg. A4. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1972 Dec 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Greenhouse Lower Side Details, Dwg. A5. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1972 Jul 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Greenhouse Upper Side Dets, Dwg. A6. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1972 Jul 7. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Sections - Greenhouse Side, At Intermediate Side Mullion, Dwg. A7. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1972 Dec 7. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Ridge and Roof Details, Dwg. A8. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1972 Dec 12. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Roof Details at Corners, Dwg. A9. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1972 Dec 29. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Mullion Dets at Corners, Dwg. A10. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1972 Dec 5. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - [Corner Details Above and Below Gutter], Dwg. A11. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1972 Dec 18. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Sill Detail at Connection of Colonial Amer. & Semi-Tropical Gardens, Dwg. A12. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1973 Jan 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Door Details of Door in West Side, Dwg. A13. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1973 Jan 3 Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Italian - Gardens, Side Ventilation Det.s, Dwg. A14. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1973 Jan 5. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Italian Gardens Reconstr'n, Roof Framing Plan, Foundation Plan. URI Dekosit/ K.C.E. 1970 Apr 13. Sepia Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Italian Gardens Reconstr'n, Section thru New Italian Gardens #24 Greenhouse. URI Dekosit/ K.C.E. 1970 Apr 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - New Cover Over Bulb CellarURI Dekosit/ M.D.S. 1970 Apr 2. Sepia Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F7, Box 119)
  - Door Details. Lord & Burnham/ R.S. 1961 Apr 24. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F8, Box 119)
  - Proposed Rehabilitation and Restoration of Tropical Garden House No. 22, Edwardian Garden House No. 26. Lord & Burnham/ F.H. 1972 Oct 4. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F8, Box 119)
  - Proposed Glass Roof. Lord & Burnham/ F.H. 1972 Apr. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F8, Box 119)
  - Proposed Blue Ribbon Greenhouse to Replace Existing House No. 3. Lord & Burnham/ F.H. 1978 Dec 15. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F8, Box 119)
  - Scale Plans & Elevs Houses #9-10 & Corridor, Dwg. #1. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1978 May 15. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F8, Box 119)
  - Sill Plan - Houses #9-#10 & Corridor, Dwg. #2. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1978 May 12. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F8, Box 119)
  - South - Side Details - New Truss Post at Existing House, Houses #9 & 10, Dwg. #3. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/E.W.K. 1978 May 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F8, Box 119)
  - South Side Details - Intermediate Bar Connection, Houses - 9 & 10, Dwg. #4. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/E.W.K. 1978 May 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F8, Box 119)
  - North Side Dets Houses #9 & 10, Dwg. #4A. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1978 May 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F8, Box 119)
  - Truss Assembly, Houses 9 & 10, Dwg. #5. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/E.W.K. 1978 May 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F8, Box 119)
  - Construction Drawing-Guardhouse for Duke Farms Plan Sections. Donald Pantel, architect. 1962 Aug 22. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F8, Box 119)
  - Roof Truss Details, Houses 9 & 10, Dwg. #6. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ E.W.K. 1978 May 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F9, Box 119)
  - Houses 9 & 10 Gable Details, Dwg. #7. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/D.D. 1978 May 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F9, Box 119)
  - South Side Corner Details, Dwg. #8. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/D.D. 1978 May 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F9, Box 119)
  - Cooling Pad System Dets, Houses #9 & #10, Dwg. #9. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/D.D. 1978 May 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F9, Box 119)
  - Blue Ribbon House, 10'-3-3/4" Bays, Standard Arm & Rod Roof Sash Operator. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ T. L. Cihi. 1969 Sep 26. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F9, Box 119)
  - RC42MT Roof Fan Details, Blue Ribbon Century Greenhouse Plans, Houses 9 & 10. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ P.S. 1978 May 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F9, Box 119)
  - Existing - Passage Conn. to New G'h'se, Dwg. #11. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1978 May 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F9, Box 119)
  - Green Houses for Mr. J. B. Duke. Horace Trumbauer, architect. 1909 Apr. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - [Tropical Gardens, Greenhouse #26], Roof Plan, Front Elevation. URI Dekosit. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - [Frame of Greenhouse 24], Section B-B. URI Dekosit. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - [Frame of Greenhouses 23 & 25]. URI Dekosit. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - Details - Italian Gardens No. 24. URI Dekosit. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - [Details and Building Specifications]. URI Dekosit. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - Italian Gardens Reconstr'n. URI Dekosit. 1970 Apr 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - [Roof Framing Plan and Floor Plan]. URI Dekosit. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - Italian Gardens - Reconstr'n. URI Dekosit. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - [Foundation Plan and Roof Framing Plan]. URI Dekosit. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - [Front and Rear Elevations]. URI Dekosit. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - Map of Water Mains and Sewers in Conj. With New Greenhouses & Sunken Garden of Est. of J.B. Duke. I J Shaffer. 1913 Sep. Blueprint, photostat. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - [Floor Plan and Roof Framing Plan]. URI Dekosit. 1970 Sep 29. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F1, Box 119)
  - [Boiler Layout]. Burnham Corporation/G. Maus. 1958 Nov 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F2, Box 119)
  - India. John R. Hecht. 1965 Jan. Pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D3F2, Box 119)
  - Proposed Connecting Passage. Lord & Burnham/L.R.W. 1960 Sep 6. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F2, Box 119)
  - Proposed New Greenhouse. Lord & Burnham/L.R.W. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F2, Box 119)
  - Proposed Connecting Passage, Proposition B. Lord & Burnham/L.R.W. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F2, Box 119)
  - Planter Box Comellia House. Undated. Pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D3F2, Box 119)
  - Indian Gardens-Lighting Wiring Plan. Nordheimer Associates; Jean Rosenthal. 1965 Dec 1. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F2, Box 119)
  - James B. Duke Esq, Somerville, NJ - Potted Fruit Houses. [Lord & Burnham]. 1912 Mar 27. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F2, Box 119)
  - James B. Duke Esq, Somerville, NJ - Potted Fruit Houses. [Lord & Burnham]. 1912 Mar 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F2, Box 119)
  - Plan of the Gardens. Innocenti & Webel. 1938 Dec 23. Positive photostat. (Opaperfolder C2D3F3, Box 119)
  - Scheme #1. Undated. Pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D3F3, Box 119)
  - Scheme #2. Undated. Pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D3F3, Box 119)
  - [Duke Gardens Houses 1-27C]. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F3, Box 119)
  - Proposed Orange Grove Enclosure. Lord & Burnham Co. 1915 Jan 7. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F3, Box 119)
  - Proposed Orange Grove Enclosure. Lord & Burnham Co. 1914 Jan 7. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F3, Box 119)
  - # B. Hill and Lake Design. H. Kay Katakawa. Undated. Pencil on illustration board. (Opaperfolder C2D3F4, Box 119)
  - Dry. Flat Garden. H. Kay Katakawa. Undated. Pencil on illustration board. (Opaperfolder C2D3F4, Box 119)
  - Design for Miss D. Duke. H. Kay Katakawa. Undated. Pencil and watercolor on illustration board. (Opaperfolder C2D3F4, Box 119)
  - Look from Tropical Room to Japanese Garden. H. Kay Katakawa. Undated. Pencil on illustration board. (Opaperfolder C2D3F4, Box 119)
  - House 17. H. Kay Katakawa. Undated. Pencil on illustration board. (Opaperfolder C2D3F4, Box 119)
  - [Duke Farm]. Rado. Undated. Watercolor. (Opaperfolder C2D3F4, Box 119)
  - For Duke Foundation [Japanese Garden]. H. Kay Katakawa. Undated. Pencil on illustration board. (Opaperfolder C2D3F5, Box 119)
  - [Japanese Garden]. H. Kay Katakawa. Undated. Pencil on illustration board. (Opaperfolder C2D3F5, Box 119)
  - [Japanese Garden]. H. Kay Katakawa. Undated. Pencil on illustration board. (Opaperfolder C2D3F5, Box 119)
  - [Japanese Garden]. H. Kay Katakawa. Undated. Pencil on illustration board. (Opaperfolder C2D3F5, Box 119)
  - [Japan]ese Garden Unfinished Map. H. Kay Katakawa. Undated. Pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D3F5, Box 119)
  - Trench Plan. 1909 Jul 8. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F7, Box 119)
  - Green Houses. Horace Trumbauer, architect. 1909 Apr. Blueprint, photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D3F7, Box 119)
  - Duke Farms, Drawn from Aerial Photo 1956 showing various houses on estate. Donald H. Stires. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F7, Box 119)
  - Alterations to Garage Duke Gardens. James S. Jones. 1959 Jul 9. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F7, Box 119)
  - Site Plan. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D3F7, Box 119)
  - Manual Conference Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. 1932 Oct 26 Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Central Office Trunk Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. 1948 Dec 22. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Cord, Telephone, Dial, Battery, Buzzer and Ringing Circuits. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Manual Conference Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Manual Conference Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Assembly, Wiring and Equipment for 100 Point Line Finder. Western Electric Company. 1949 Apr 14. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Framework Insulating Details and Dust Sealing Details. Western Electric Company. 1949 Dec 5. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Framework for Mounting Traffic Registers in Jack Field. Western Electric Company. 1954 Jun 23. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - 555 & 556A Non-Multiple Switchboard, Section Assembly. Western Electric Company. 1954 Jul 7. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - 555A & 556A Non Multiple Switchboard, Steel Frame Assembly. Western Electric Company. 1954 Aug 2. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Battery Cut Off Circuit. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Toll Diversion, Busy Tone and Dial Tone Circuits. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Framework Terminal Strip A3, 1st Frame - 50 Line System, 1st or 2nd Frame - 100 Line System, Wiring Layout. Western Electric Company. 1961 Oct 26. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Local Cabling Plan for Modified 556A Switchboard. Western Electric Company. 1962 Jan 8. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Specification for 50 or 100 Line Manual or Key-Lite Frame Equipment. Western Electric Company. Undated. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D3F8, Box 119)
  - Assembly, Wiring and Equipment for Hunting Selector-Connector. Western Electric Company. 1959 May 22. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F1, Box 119)
  - Line Finder Circuit, Station Finder Circuit, Selector-Connector Circuit, Connector Circuit, Wiring of Jacks. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F1, Box 119)
  - Line Finder Circuit, Station Finder Circuit, Wiring of Banks and Commutators, Selector-Connector Circuit, Connection Circuit, Wiring of Banks. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F1, Box 119)
  - Framework Terminal Strip B, 1st Frame - 50 Line System, 1st or 2nd Frame - 100 Line System, Wiring Layout. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 19. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F1, Box 119)
  - Framework Terminal Strip C, 1st Frame - 50 or 100 Line System, Without Key-Lite Swbd, Wiring Layout. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 19. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F1, Box 119)
  - Trunk Circuit Cabling, DDCO CDCO & ATT Trunks. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 19. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F1, Box 119)
  - Assembly, Wiring and Equipment for Hunting Selector-Connector or Inter-Frame Connector. Western Electric Company. 1961 Apr 25. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F1, Box 119)
  - Trunk to Attendant Circuit for Use With Key Lite or Cord Switchboard. Western Electric Company. 1961 Apr 29. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F1, Box 119)
  - Framework Terminal Strip B2, 1st Frame - 50 Line System Without Key-Lite or 100 Line System With or Without Key-Lite. Western Electric Company. 1961 Aug 18. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F1, Box 119)
  - Framework Terminal Strip B1, 1st Frame - 50 Line System, 1st or 2nd Frame - 100 Line System, Wiring Layout. Western Electric Company. 1961 Aug 18. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F1, Box 119)
  - Framework Terminal Strip B3, 1st Frame - 50 or 100 Line System Without KeyLite or 1st Frame - 100 Line System with KeyLite, Wiring Layout. Western Electric Company. 1961 Aug 21. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F1, Box 119)
  - Modified 556A PBX for Use in 740-BE PBX, Jack Figure Circuits. Western Electric Company. 1961 Oct 16. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F1, Box 119)
  - Telephone & Dial Circuit. Western Electric Company. 1949 May 2. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - Battery, Buzzer and Ringing Circuits. Western Electric Company. 1949 Sep 2. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - One Way Trunk Circuit to Central Office Outgoing Dial Selected or No. 701A or 740E, Two Way Trunk Circuit to Central Office Manual or Dial Selected. Western Electric Company. 1954 Jan 14. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - One Way Trunk Circuit to Central Office Outgoing Dial Selected or No. 701A or 740E, Two Way Trunk Circuit to Central Office Manual or Dial Selected. Western Electric Company. 1954 Jan 14. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - OG Co Trk or 2W Co Trk. Western Electric Company. 1954 Jan 14. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - OG Co Trk or 2W Co Trk. Western Electric Company. 1954 Jan 14. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - OG Co Trk or 2W Co Trk. Western Electric Company. 1954 Jan 14. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - OG Co Trk or 2W Co Trk. Western Electric Company. 1954 Jan 14. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - OG Co Trk or 2W Co Trk. Western Electric Company. 1954 Jan 14. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - OG Co Trk or 2W Co Trk. Western Electric Company. 1954 Jan 14. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - One Way Trunk Circuit to Central Office Outgoing Dial Selected or No. 701A or 740E, Two Way Trunk Circuit to Central Office Manual or Dial Selected. Western Electric Company. 1954 Jan 14. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - Cord Circuit D3 Wiring. Western Electric Company. 1955 Oct 19. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - Manual Conference Circuit Arranged for a Maximum of 4 or 5 Simultaneous Connections. Western Electric Company. 1957 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - Jack Figures Circuit (Dwg 30). Western Electric Company. 1961 Oct 16. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - Jack Figures Circuit (Dwg 31). Western Electric Company. 1961 Oct 16. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - Jack Figures Circuit (Dwg 32). Western Electric Company. 1961 Oct 16. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F2, Box 119)
  - Attendant Trunk Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Estate Map. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Wiring List. Undated. Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Alarm Circuit. Western Electric Company. 1956 Mar 28. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Specification for Telephone Circuit D3 Wiring. Western Electric Company. 1956 Sep 10. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Central Office Trunk Circuit. Western Electric Company. 1957 Mar 18. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Attendant Trunk Circuit from Selector or Selector Connector Levels. Western Electric Company. 1957 Dec 2. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Attendant Trunk Circui. Western Electric Company. 1957 Dec 2. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Assembly, Wiring and Equipment for Hunting Selector-Connector. Western Electric Company. 1959 May 22. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Station Line Circuit Arranged for Transfer to Central Office Trunks During Power Failure. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Line Finder Circuit, Group Alarm & Test Key, Sub-Group, Test & Make Busy Jacks and Test Line Jack. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Alarm Circuit. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 12. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Battery, Buzzer and Ringing Circuits. Western Electric Company. 1961 Jun 29. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Manual Conference Circuit Arranged for a Maximum of 4 or 5 Simultaneous Connections. Western Electric Company. 1963 Jun 12. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - PBX Systems (Dwg B1). Western Electric Company. 1963 Jun 12. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - PBX Systems (Dwg B2). Western Electric Company. 1963 Jun 12. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - PBX Systems (Dwg B3). Western Electric Company. 1963 Jun 12. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - Attendant Trunk Circuit. Western Electric Company. [1957 Dec 2]. Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - [Battery, Buzzer and Ringing Circuits]. Western Electric Company. [Circa 1961]. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F3, Box 119)
  - One Way Trunk Circuit, No. - 701A, 701B, 701PK or 740E, 2 Way Trunk Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. 1957 May 15. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - One Way Trunk Circuit, No. - 701A, 701B, 701PK or 740E, 2 Way Trunk Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - One Way Trunk Circuit, No. - 701A, 701B or 740E, 2 Way Trunk Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - Toll Diversion, Busy Tone, Dial Tone Circuits. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - Station Line Circuit Arranged for Transfer to Central Office Trunks During Power Failure. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - Group Alarm & Test Key, Sub-Group, Test & Make Busy Jacks and Test Line Jack Circuits. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - Alarm Circuit. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - Test Line Circuit for Test of Sel-Conn and Key-Lite Swbd Circuits. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - Traffic Register Circuit. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - Test Line Circuit for Test of Sel-Conn and Key-Lite Swbd Circuits. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 11. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - Traffic Register Circuit. Western Electric Company. 1959 Dec 2. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - Battery Cut-Off Circuit. Western Electric Company. 1959 Dec 2. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - Trunk To Attendant for Use with Key-Lite or Cord Switchboard. Western Electric Company. 1961 May 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - Trunk To Attendant for Use with Key-Lite or Cord Switchboard. Western Electric Company. 1961 May 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F4, Box 119)
  - One Way Trunk Circuit, No. - 701A, 701B, 701PK or 740E, 2 Way Trunk Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)